The caption of Table 4, as published, states:

"Average in-degree, average out-degree, maximum in-degree and maximum out-degree for each 
component. Each figure is the average across all networks in 2006."

The caption should instead read: 

"Average unweighted in-clustering coefficient, unweighted out-clustering coefficient,
weighted in-clustering coefficient, and weighted out-clustering coefficient for each
component. Each figure is the average across all networks in 2006."

